
var easyQuestions = [
  { //q1
    question: 'What soap opera did Joey star in?',
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Days of Our Lives',
      'b) One Life to Live',
      'c) General Hospital',
      'd) Passions'
    ],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) Days of Our Lives'
  },

  { //q2
    question: 'Whose name did Ross say at the altar?',
    possibleAnswers: ['a) Emily', 'b) Phoebe', 'c) Rachel', 'd) Susan'],
    flags: [false, false, true, false],
    answer: 'c) Rachel'
  },

  { //q3
    question: "What is the name of Central Perk's barista?",
    possibleAnswers: ['a) Adam', 'b) Paolo', 'c) Mark', 'd) Gunther'],
    flags: [false, false, false, true],
    answer: 'd) Gunther'
  },

  { //q4
    question: "What is Joey's signature pick-up-line?",
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) How are you doing?',
      'b) Have I seen you on tv?',
      "c) How's it going?",
      "d) How you doin'?"
    ],
    flags: [false, false, false, true],
    answer: "d) How you doin'?"
  },

  { //q5
    question: "What is Ross' profession?",
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Paleontologist',
      'b) Doctor',
      'c) Advertisor',
      'd) Actor'
    ],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) Paleontologist'
  },

  { //q6
    question: 'Where does the show take place?',
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) New York City',
      'b) Los Angeles',
      'c) San Francisco',
      'd) Seattle'
    ],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) New York City'
  },

  { //q7
    question: 'How many seasons of Friends are there?',
    possibleAnswers: ['a) 8', 'b) 7', 'c) 9', 'd) 10'],
    flags: [false, false, false, true],
    answer: 'd) 10'
  },

  { //q8
    question: 'How many Friends are there?',
    possibleAnswers: ['a) 6', 'b) 7', 'c) 5', 'd) 4'],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) 6'
  },

  { //q9
    question: 'How many times has Ross been married?',
    possibleAnswers: ['a) 3', 'b) 0', 'c) 2', 'd) 1'],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) 3'
  },

  { //q10
    question: 'What actress plays Rachel?',
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Jennifer Garner',
      'b) Jennifer Aniston',
      'c) Courteney Cox',
      'd) Lisa Kudrow'
    ],
    flags: [false, true, false, false],
    answer: 'b) Jennifer Aniston'
  },

  { //q11
    question: 'Where do the Friends always hang out?',
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Central Park',
      'b) Central Perk',
      'c) A Bar',
      "d) Phoebe's apartment"
    ],
    flags: [false, true, false, false],
    answer: 'b) Central Perk'
  },

  { //q12
    question: "What is Chandler's last name?",
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Geller',
      'b) Green',
      'c) Bing',
      'd) Tribbiani'
    ],
    flags: [false, false, true, false],
    answer: 'c) Bing'
  },

  { //q13
    question: "What is Phoebe's signature song?",
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Smelly Cat',
      'b) You Suck',
      'c) Stinky Dog',
      'd) Pervert Parade'
    ],
    flags: [true, false, false, false],
    answer: 'a) Smelly Cat'
  },

  { //q14
    question: 'Who does Monica marry?',
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Richard',
      'b) Fun Bobby',
      'c) Chandler',
      'd) Joey'
    ],
    flags: [false, false, true, false],
    answer: 'c) Chandler'
  },

  { //q15
    question: "Who was involved in the 'We Were On a Break' fight?",
    possibleAnswers: [
      'a) Monica and Chandler',
      'b) Phoebe and Mike',
      'c) Ross and Mona',
      'd) Ross and Rachel'
    ],
    flags: [false, false, false, true],
    answer: 'd) Ross and Rachel'
  }
]

  // { q16
  //   question: 'Who does Joey play on Days of Our Lives?',
  //   possibleAnswers: [
  //     'a) Dr. Striker Ramore',
  //     'b) Dr. Drake Ramore',
  //     'c) Dr. Hans Ramore',
  //     'd) Dr. Anthony Ramore'
  //   ],
  //   flags: [false, true, false, false],
  //   answer: 'b) Dr. Drake Ramore'
  // }
  // Commented out code should not be in production branch
  // Really well organized data for the questions.  Good use of objects and arrays.  I'm learning so much about Friends!
